Russ Altman: Hey everyone, it's your host
Russ Altman from The Future of Everything.
You know, about a year ago, our team
was in New York where we taped a live
episode of The Future of Everything.
It was with computer scientist
Fei-Fei Li, and economists
Susan Athey and Neale Mahoney.
We talked about how AI is reshaping
innovation, creativity, jobs, and public
policy, and the economy in general.
So we thought we would play it again.
You know, this episode won us a Webby
Award, and so we're pretty proud of it,
and we hope you'll enjoy taking a listen
This is Stanford Engineering's
The Future of Everything, and
I'm your host, Russ Altman.
Today we're taping the show live
at the Glass House in New York
City in front of a live audience.
If you enjoy The Future of
Everything, please hit follow in
whatever app you're listening to.
This will guarantee you that
you never miss an episode.
Today, Fei-Fei Li, Neale Mahoney, and
Susan Athey will tell us that AI is
enabling tremendous creativity in new
products and services, but we need to
focus on its impact on humans through
appropriate policies, safety nets,
in order to have the best outcomes.
It's the future of the innovation economy.
Also, we're continuing, uh, a new segment
in the show called The Future in a Minute.
I will ask my guests some
rapid-fire questions, and they
will provide rapid-fire answers.
Uh, and we'll do this at the end, uh,
after the end of our conversation.
And before we get started, please
remember to follow the show on whatever
app you're listening to because you
never wanna miss the future of anything.
Okay, we're getting started
about innovation economy.
Uh, and it's useful to
define what it means.
Of course, in preparation for the
show, I did what we would all do.
I went to a large language model.
I went to three, ChatGPT, Claude, and
Perplexity, just 'cause I have those URLs.
Perplexity was my favorite.
It said, "The innovation economy refers
to an economic system where growth is
primarily driven by the generation,
application, and commercialization of new
ideas, products, and technologies, rather
than the more traditional heavy reliance
on physical assets and manual labor."
And then they go on to say that
applications, examples might
include ride sharing, house sharing,
social media, and many others.
Now, although the innovation economy is
not entirely about artificial intelligence
or AI, AI is a very big part of it
and a part where our panel is expert.
Questions that arise for AI and the
innovation economy are, what will be
the impact on jobs, on the quality
of life, on the overall economy?
And how do we navigate a future in a way
that, uh, protects all humans but enables
unbelievable beneficial innovations?
Today, my three guests
will help us understand the
opportunities and challenges.
They are all professors
at Stanford University.
Fei-Fei Li is a professor of
computer science, Neale Mahoney is
a professor of economics, and Susan
Athey is a professor of business.
This is the innovation economy dream team.
Susan, let's get started.
You have written that AI is a
general purpose technology, and so
its impacts are likely to be broad
and very difficult to predict.
But you have looked in your work at
other general purpose technologies
that have emerged in the past.
What did we learn from
when these things emerge?
Susan Athey: Looking back from everything
from electricity and industrialization
to the personal computer, which a lot
of us have lived through, um, they can
have really profound impacts locally,
but yet not show up in big changes
in GDP growth for quite some time.
And there are many reasons for this, but
a big lesson from the past is that when
you unlock one bottleneck you find others.
And to fully make use of a technology,
you may need to restructure industries,
but certainly restructure production
in or- order to fully optimize for it.
Russ Altman: I take it that these
bottlenecks can come up, like,
in all different places and in
all different aspects of the
economy and the, and the business?
Susan Athey: That's right.
So of course, people, every… Many
economists talk about AI in general
as a general purpose technology.
One that is less discussed, but I think
profound, is that software development
is a general purpose technology.
In general, digitization is something
that restructures industries, and
it helps small enterprises scale.
It increases the span of control.
It allows firms to grow without just
having to directly supervise people.
That kind of general purpose technology,
though, has not been fully adopted.
It's, i- across the world, many
small businesses are less digitized.
It's, and it's generally been something
with a lot of scale economies, especially
with data and machine learning.
The challenges have been that there's
a lot of fixed costs to get going.
If you're running a restaurant off
of paper or maybe WhatsApp or WeChat,
um, there's a, there's a- another leap.
You have to be big enough to
justify those investments.
Um, and so one of the things you might
ask today is, all right, w- what would
happen if we removed the bottleneck
that software engineering was?
If you talk to a, a bank in Wisconsin or
even, you know, in Brazil or Argentina,
and they say, "Well, are we, are we
doing enough with machine learning?"
And you would find out that, well, they
have a lot of trouble hiring people.
They have a lot of, of trouble
getting… Be- being able to adopt.
And I might recommend five, 10
years ago that really it, it…
You may not get that much value
quickly from making big investments
'cause it takes so long to get going.
So there, there were many
bottlenecks around just getting
data organized in the past.
One of the things that, um, that when
you look out in companies, they're
using clunky software if they're,
if they're even using it at all,
because it's so hard to change that
you, you change rarely and you put
a lot of effort into it when you do.
So the bottlenecks have been around
adoption, figuring out what you want
given that you're gonna be stuck
with it, and just the big cost.
So now we have to ask, if
software development is actually
very cheap now, what stops us?
If it makes it really… If, if, if
we could already build today, say, a
nursing assistant that could be very
effective, especially in a country
where nurses aren't well-trained and
there's not a lot of education, why
do we think that it's not actually
gonna be fully adopted tomorrow?
And you can think of many reasons actually
that it won't be fully adopted tomorrow.
You have to decide what to do.
You have to get the nurses on board.
You would have to train them.
It's, it's hard to adopt
something new, and so you wouldn't
just pick the first thing up.
And so yet I don't predict that
next year there will be nursing
assistants around the world.
Russ Altman: Great.
Thank you.
So on this issue of, uh, bottlenecks
and jobs, Neale, you have taken
a long view in some of your work
on the impact of AI on jobs.
Um, how do you think about either
predicting or measuring the impact
of AI on the labor market i-in some
of the examples that Susan just said?
Neale Mahoney: Yeah, so
it's a great question.
I sort of joke that the two questions
I get the most as a economist in
Silicon Valley is what jobs is AI gonna
disrupt and what do we do about it?
I tell them I have no clue on what
jobs are gonna be disrupted, but I
know exactly what to do about it.
Russ Altman: Boom.
Neale Mahoney: Um, so- … boom.
W-what should we do about it?
Uh, I think we're facing sort of a
veil of ignorance moment, so, you know,
connecting to, uh, the humanities.
I think many of you remember
Rawls's thought experiment
of the veil of ignorance.
If we can step back from our current
lives and think about before we
have our endowments, our skills,
oh, what do we want in society?
What protections and safeguards
do we want in society?
And I think that's where we are with AI,
that we know that some of us, uh, may lose
a job or may have human capital, which
is less valuable on the labor market.
We don't know who it's gonna
be, and I think what Rawls tells
us is now is the right time to
invest in a social safety net.
I'll give you one example,
and then I'll shut up.
Um, right, we live in a country
where if you lose your job- You
likely lose your health insurance.
Uh, you know, maybe I'm
wearing my political hat.
I think that's crazy now.
Uh, it is going to be hugely crazy
when 5, 10% of us lose our primary
occupation, maybe, because of AI.
So, so thinking about how, oh, we're
in a veil of ignorance moment, and
how we can invest in a social safety
net to protect us against, I think,
the disruption w- we will face i-
is a hugely important endeavor.
Russ Altman: Thank you, and I wanna come
back to safety nets a little bit later.
Fei-Fei, you're a technologist who
helped shepherd in the AI revolution.
You're working currently in the area
of visual intelligence and spatial
intelligence far beyond what the
current things like ChatGPT, uh, and
all the, and all the others, uh, go do.
But these are also areas where
living organisms li- on Earth,
like humans, have been excellent.
We've evolved to be excellent at space.
We've been evolved to be
excellent at seeing things.
How do you think the s- kind of systems
you and others are building will interact
with the humans who are using them?
Or how do you hope that will happen?
Fei-Fei Li: Yeah, thanks for the question.
So, uh, first of all, I, I do agree
right now we're at the, uh, dawn of
a AI economy, and I think whether
it's the large language models or
the f- next chapters, which are the
spatial intelligence models, the,
uh, the embodied AI models, we're
gonna see more and more innovation
in, uh, in, uh, in this technology
going beyond what we're seeing now.
One thing that, um, also living in
Silicon Valley, also getting the same
questions that Neale does, that puzzles
me is that when people talk about AI,
they go straight to the word replacement.
replacing humans.
And this is just, we got to be
a little careful because AI,
they're, AI will change jobs.
AI, AI will change different
tasks within a complex job.
For example, being a
nurse in a nursing home.
There are hundreds of daily
tasks a nurse, uh, does.
AI will help some, but will not,
uh, replace the, the, uh, the
job wholesale, uh, wholesaly.
What is really important is to recognize,
instead of replacing, AI really augments.
And that's what I really believe, is
that this is a horizontal technology
that can superpower humans, superpower
our workflow, augment so many
capabilities that humans are good at.
We are l- l- we might be short of labor,
or we might not be so good at particular
part of that jo- a, a capability,
but with AI, uh, it can help us.
I want to just take one example
because I'm in the area of, uh,
visual-spatial intelligence.
We work with cre- uh, creators, you know,
visual creators, storytellers, movie,
uh, makers, filmmakers, game developers.
All of these creators are facing
this, a new era of AI tools.
And it's so incredible for me to
meet and work with them because they
see AI as a tool to augment them.
They see AI as a way to supercharge
their creativity and their productivity.
So I'm not trying to say that
there's not a double-edged sword.
We should talk about that.
But I do think it's so important
we recognize that this technology
can do a lot more to supercharge,
superpower people, putting people
in the center instead of go
straight to the word replacement.
Russ Altman: Thank
Neale Mahoney: you.
Can I, can I jump in on this?
Russ Altman: Yes.
Neale Mahoney: One, I agree.
And two, I think a useful framework
is, you know, if you think about the
questions in innovation policy over the
20th century or early part of the 21st
century, they're about how do we maximize
innovation given budgetary constraints,
human, um, capital constraints.
Uh, but moving forward, I think the
most interesting, richest questions
will be less about just sort of
how do we, uh, put our foot on the
gas, but how do we shape innovation
to be complementary to our skills?
And that's, that's a STEM question,
but it's also a humanities question.
Yeah.
Because it requires tapping into
what are the activities that
give us meaning and purpose.
And so, you know, at Stanford campus,
where we have that intersection of
the humanities and STEM, I think
is a great place to be working on
that hugely important question.
Fei-Fei Li: It's the
human-centered AI question.
Neale Mahoney: Yeah.
Somebody named the- … their
institute very well.
Susan Athey: Yeah.
And yeah, and I think we have… You know,
Fei-Fei and I worked together, um, when,
and Russ, with, with the, the founding
of the Stanford Institute for, for- And
Fei-Fei Li: John
Susan Athey: too … Human-Centered
AI, and John Levin as well.
Um, and one of our theses was exactly,
you know, developing this idea, what is
the role of a university in all of this?
And of course, commercial interests are
often purely profit, which is lowering
cost, but a lot of these innovations
are fixed cost in- investments.
So if you invent a nursing
assistant, you know, it can be
applied and adapted in many places.
And so if we do some of the innovation
in the university for human augmenting
technology, then that takes care of some
of the fixed costs, and then entrepreneurs
can take it across the finish line and
solve the last mile adoption problem.
And that can happen, not just us
building something and throwing it
over the transom, but one of the
great things about the language-based
AI is that actually many people can
participate in it, even if they don't
have a big computer science background.
Um, and so actually we can see the
participation and the value add
coming, you know, across the world
and figuring out how to help it
augment humans in those settings.
And I just wanted to connect
something that came across all of
us, which is that, um, government
policy also can play a role in this.
And so when people ask me, like, "What
are all the people gonna do? Are they
just gonna sit on the beach and have
drones drop them daiquiris?" Well-
Neale Mahoney: I hope so.
Susan Athey: I mean, I have many questions
about how we get to the beach and why
the drones are bringing us daiquiris.
But- … if we put that… If we, if we
take a slightly nearer term view, there
are many activities that scale with the
size of populations and where we are
sort of under-investing in them today.
More childcare, more nursing,
better doctors, better elder care.
You know, all of those things are
th- are things that humans could be
productively employed at, at large scale.
And AI can help humans transition
into those jobs, and governments
can procure those things.
Governments have a big role in
investing in all of those sectors.
So like, rather than imagining like just
a bunch of people not doing anything,
if we get ourselves organized, we
create the products, we create the
government policy, then in principle, we
can help people through the transition
while making all of us better off.
So
Russ Altman: Susan, you spent two years
in government, I happen to know, and
I know that you're an advisor and a,
and a research associate, uh, Neale.
Tell me, with your real world
understanding of the government
today, how's that gonna go?
Susan Athey: You know, it's, it- it's
really hard because w- at this moment,
right, like we've, we've had the last
six years or so have … We've had
some curve balls thrown at us, and
it- it's not easy to figure out the
very best thing to do in the face
of big changes and big disruptions.
Um, it's really hard, and it's … And
so, you know, we need to, we need to
work together on solving those problems.
And so, you know, it is scary to think
about our government getting less
functional in the face of places where
actually government leadership might be,
for both research, for, for universities,
could be more essential, um, than ever.
Russ Altman: Thanks.
Fei-Fei Li: I, I just
want to add something.
You know, um, I firmly believe
100 years from now when historians
rewrite the chapters of 21st century,
especially the dawn of AI, a collective
success of humanity or this country
would be that this era of AI, uh,
launched a revolution in education.
Is that now that AI, even language
models, has proven that AI can do the
standardized tests by and large to, to
whatever passing or even excellent grades,
that we should rethink about spending 10,
more than 12 years of human capital, that
educating young humans to evaluate them
to the level of what AI can do today.
Human education should be completely
rethought because AI c- showed us
that it's not about, uh, you know,
memorization of kn- uh, knowledge and
evaluation of these memorizations.
So if there's anything government can
do, to me, is the investment of K12
education as well as higher education,
'cause this is the moment that we can
really revolutionize the most important
thing on Earth, which is human capital.
Neale Mahoney: Neale?
I'm gonna-
Um, I want to connect these
threads a-and run with it.
Uh, there's a great fact from the
economist David Autor, uh, who's
documented that, you know, over 70 years,
something like 70% of the occupations
we have in the economy sort of emerge.
That is, if you look back 70 years
ago, uh, 70% of jobs didn't exist.
So, you know, if AI diffuses in a way
which I think is g-geographically spread
out and not too fast, that we will adapt.
We hopefully will come up with
new ways to educate people to
be complementary to that AI.
AI will adapt in ways which
are complementary to humans.
Uh, but history also teaches us that
when things are concentrated and rapid
So if you think about the hollowing
out of factory towns, uh, due to
Chinese accession in, in the WTO and
automation, those impacts can be,
uh, devastating, and we need policy
to come in and provide a safety net.
So I don't know which timeline we're on.
We're probably some combination of
the two, but I think thinking about
those extremes and sort of shaping the
technology and education is sort of useful
to triangulate in a uncertain future.
Russ Altman: Thanks.
And now, Fei-Fei, I want you to put your
hat on as somebody who has a startup,
and you're trying to make a go of it.
And then we're talking about safety nets.
We're talking about governmental policies.
I'm sure you have part of yourself
and your, and your, and your cohort
that gets worried that there will
be premature regulation, premature
policies that actually take away your
ability to do the things you wanna do.
What--how does that conversation go,
and, and how do you think about it?
Fei-Fei Li: Uh, great question.
First of all, I'm still partially, uh,
involved in Stanford, so I'm not 100%
on leave, just to make it very clear.
And, uh, it's also, um, one of the most
fascinating conversations that has been
happening in the state of California
as well as, uh, uh, federally about
the, the tension between AI regulation
and, uh, and AI, um, innovation.
And, uh, you know, I wanna start with,
I'm a parent, and, uh, when your child
is about the age of, I don't know, six
or seven, one of the most important
lessons you need to teach them is to
turn on the stove and cook an egg.
And that's to, you know, use fire.
And, uh, and it's a pretty
dangerous thing, right?
But you all have to bite the bullet
and teach your kid to, um, use fire.
And then there are many other
things we have to teach our kids.
Uh, the reason I'm using this is that,
uh, uh, this example is technology
is always a double-edged sword.
That's since the dawn
of human civilization.
We, in our DNA, we're compelled to
innovate so we can live and work better,
but we also use that to sometimes
inadvertently hurt ourselves or sometimes
purpo- intentionally hurt each other.
No matter what, that tension between
the drive for innovation and the need
for establishing norms and, uh, and
guardrails is always gonna be there.
So as an entrepreneur, as an innovator,
I think it's very important that
we arrive at a healthy balance.
And, uh, with Stanford HAI, we have
been actually advocating a policy
framework for AI, which is very simple,
is first science, no science fiction.
You know, to do good regulatory or
government policy, we should use data,
use measurement, like what Susan has
been doing in government, um, to, to
guide our regulatory fram- framework
instead of those far-fetched sci-
science fiction extinction doomsday.
Second is that be pragmatic,
not ideological, right?
For example, um, in AI, we have so
many, uh, regulatory frameworks.
You're involved with the healthcare FDA.
And, and we should just maximize the,
the, the interaction and partnership
with these pragmatic frameworks
ins- instead of going ideological.
And last but not the least, um, in
this audience, I always believed
invest in our public sector,
invest in our innovation engine.
Like Condi said, there's no plan B. Go-
uh, government, uh, policy in AI should
include the investment of our country's,
uh, innovative engines, including the h-
uh, universities and, uh, public sector.
Russ Altman: Thank you.
And, and I, I actually wanna go to a
slightly different topic, but Susan,
uh, you, you were in the Justice
Department for a couple years.
And in all the examples of innovation
economy successes that I gave in my
intro, social media, ride-sharing,
home-sharing, the winners have tended to
be either monopolies or near monopolies.
Um, is this a feature of
the innovation economy?
Or, or, or how should w- And
are we okay, uh, with it, or
is it not a necessary feature?
Susan Athey: I think that we, we have
often concentration because of the
scale economies, but I do think we have
examples where, um, even a little bit of
competition is a lot better than none.
And we h- we have seen a lot
of concerns when One firm can
put a tax on the whole economy.
I mean, and probably there's some
people here in the credit card industry,
but that's, like, sort of an easy
example because, you know, there's
a few basis points coming off of,
you know, every transaction, right?
Russ Altman: I've heard it
referred to as a toll booth.
Susan Athey: Yes.
Um, and so in the end, you know,
when those tolls get too high,
that is also bad for innovation.
So I think you can, you can think about,
uh, you know, we need, um, firms to be
able to get returns from their innovation
in order to want to do the innovation.
But then if one firm stops, slows
down all the innovation around it,
that can be problematic as well.
So I think here there's a f- I have a
few comments about competition in AI.
One is that there was a bit of a push
to hold back open models, um, open
source models, but those things can,
can… Although people were scared of
them, they can pull down the prices
for everybody, and that means that
every single business in the country
that is using large language models
can get them at lower price if there's
a free alternative that's pretty good.
And so that can be very impactful.
That conversation changed once D-
once DeepSeek came out, but still,
we, we also need to worry about,
um, other kinds of market power.
There are lots of
potential for bottleneck.
When I think especially about smaller
countries, the countries that aren't
going to themselves be generating the
profit from the AI stack, there's a
huge risk if those countries are buying
AI at sort of a high price and then
automating a lot of their labor, they
might have real wages fall because
if they're paying a lot for the AI
services, their goods prices don't fall.
So stuff people buy stays
expensive while wages fall.
So that's gonna be a really bad
situation for countries and economies.
And so if this is something that,
like, every small and big business
is going to buy, like, the price
of that thing is very important.
The quality's important.
The price is important, too.
So at the moment, it seems like we're
doing reasonably well at that, but
keeping our, our eye on the ball
to make sure that this technology
is actually gonna allow everyone to
innovate on top of it will be crucial.
Russ Altman: Uh, uh, thanks.
And, and Neale, on that note, you've been
looking at the innovation economy, uh, and
economy more general, and you've expressed
wonder about whether America and Americans
are in something of an economic funk.
And I can't help but think of that
after, after Susan's comments.
What do you mean by this economic
funt- funk, and do you see a way out?
Neale Mahoney: So if you look at
data, uh, there was a piece in The
Wall Street Journal, I think it was
now nine days ago, that documented
belief in the American Dream had gone
from 70% of the population to 25%
of the population over a generation.
Uh, that optimism about our
economy has It, it cratered after
COVID, and it hasn't recovered.
Uh, what's going on?
I think we're still figuring it out.
Uh, probably some combination
of, of three things.
Uh, one is there are, I think,
real risks in the economy.
Uh, tariffs, people concerned
about, uh, uptick in unemployment.
Uh, two, uh, I… It has to be
true that, that social media is
skewing our vision of, um, what
is a good and meaningful life.
Uh, I, I quipped that like on Instagram
you see more selfies from the Ritz
than the Motel 6, and that gives
people, uh, a unbalanced view of what
is normal and what is successful.
Uh, but I think there's
a lot we don't know.
Uh, but look, these, uh, these
conversations, I think political
leaders, innovators, um, I think
are, are all like really important in
helping this country get its mojo back.
Russ Altman: Thank you.
Hopefully.
Well, I think we're gonna
have to leave it there.
I know we want more, but
we only have 26 minutes.
Uh, this discussion has been fantastic,
but before we finish up, as promised,
I want our, move to our new segment
called The Future in a Minute.
I will ask you some quick questions,
and I'm praying that you will
give me some quick answers.
So we're gonna, we're gonna start with
Fei-Fei, and the first question is… I'm
gonna do both questions for each of you.
Uh, what is one thing that gives
you the most hope about the future?
Fei-Fei Li: Well, it's
unequivalently humanity.
There's nothing artificial
about artificial intelligence.
And I wanna paraphrase Dr. King,
that the arc of history is long, but
it bends towards benevolence, and I
believe the hope of AI is in humanity.
Russ Altman: If you were starting
over again and you needed to get
your degree or training in some
other discipline, what would it be?
Fei-Fei Li: Okay, I gotta use 30 seconds.
Six weeks ago, a Stanford sophomore
interview me, and as usual, as a
professor, I'm like, "What is your major?"
And the, the student said, "No, none
of these majors are good at Stanford."
"I'm gonna have my own major.
So I'll create my own m- major,"
which you are allowed to do.
And I ask him, "What are you gonna
create?" He said, "I'm just gonna use
AI to maximize money-making for me."
I was like, "Damn, why
didn't I have that idea?"
So, okay, my real answer would
be, if I were to start again,
I would do a combination of
physics, computer science, and art
Russ Altman: Thank you.
Neale
Fei-Fei Li: My own major though, just…
Russ Altman: Neale, what is one thing that
gives you the most hope about the future?
Neale Mahoney: Uh, I was gonna
say students, incredible students.
Uh, but this morning I was chasing
around my kids, uh, 11- and a
seven-year-old, at the American Museum
of Natural History, and seeing dozens,
hundreds of little kids excited about
STEM, about history, about dinosaurs.
Uh, we face headwinds as innovators, but
if we reflect on, on the fact that inside
we're seven-year-old boys and girls that
like dinosaurs, we're gonna be all right.
So,
Russ Altman: um- … that's where- If
you were starting over again and you
needed to get your degree or training in
a different discipline, what would it be?
Neale Mahoney: Uh, robotics.
I care about the overlap between
STEM and science and the real world.
That's why I studied economics,
but I think robotics is another
great field for that intersection.
Fei-Fei Li: Neale, you can come to my lab.
Neale Mahoney: I would love to.
Russ Altman: Susan, what is- I'm gonna
Neale Mahoney: hold you up.
Russ Altman: Susan, what is one thing that
gives you the most hope for the future?
Susan Athey: So I, I do think that
AI is more accessible and has more
potential to be helpful across
countries and across the income
distribution than the previous rounds
of technology like machine learning.
I think that it can allow small
businesses, people who don't code, who
don't build Excel spreadsheets, and don't
buy enterprise software to run a business
through a chat application and natural
language, and to grow and scale and get
more efficient, and that that can help
people rise up, um, out of poverty, and,
and it can help poor countries grow.
Russ Altman: If you were starting
over again and you needed to get your
degree or training in a different
discipline, what would it be?
Susan Athey: So I've had
to do this twice already.
Um, I trained myself in machine
learning and AI technical work,
and then I also had to learn law.
But, um, if I to- … One more thing
if I wanted to add it to the mix, I
think going forward, anybody's gonna
be able to build a great product.
If you have a good idea, you're gonna
be able to make it reality in the
digital space, so product management.
Russ Altman: Thanks to Susan Athey-
… Neale Mahoney, and Fei-Fei Li.
That was the future of
the innovation economy.
Thank you for tuning into this episode.
Thanks to our live audience for
supporting us and the show today.
With nearly 300 episodes in our back
archive catalog, you have instant access
to hours, if not days, of interesting
discussions on the future of everything.
If you're enjoying the show
or if it's helped you in any
way, not the highest bar-
Please consider rating and reviewing it.
We love to get a 5.0, but
only if we deserve it.
You can connect with me on many
social media, uh, apps, including
LinkedIn, Threads, Bluesky, and
Mastodon, @RBAltman or @RussBAltman,
where I share about every episode.
You can also follow Stanford
Engineering on social media at
StanfordSchoolOfEngineering,
or my favorite, at StanfordENG.
Cut.